urbandictionary.com 2015-12-31

# Urban Dictionary: Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy** _

Urban Dictionary, LLC ("Urban Dictionary", "we" or "us") collects (a) the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, (b) aggregate information concerning what pages users access or visit, (c) information volunteered by the user (such as survey information and/or site registrations) and (d) information related to your use of the site, including IP address, geographic location and date and time of your request. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

* It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law. 

* We transfer information about you if Urban Dictionary is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Urban Dictionary will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

* We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

* We provide such information to third parties who have entered into non-disclosure agreements with us. 

* We provide such information to a company controlled by, or under common control with, Urban Dictionary for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

**Information Gathering and Usage**

When you submit a posting to Urban Dictionary we ask for information such as your email address and name. Urban Dictionary uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use some Urban Dictionary services. Urban Dictionary and its ad management partners ("Ad Partners") use cookies to record current session information. 

Our Ad Partners may also from time to time use web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons are provided by our Ad Partners and allow Ad Partners to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page and the information in cookies set by the Ad Partners. Web beacons enable our Ad Partners to recognize a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Website. 

With both cookies and web beacon technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics data collection with the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

**Data Storage**

Urban Dictionary uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Urban Dictionary. Urban Dictionary owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Urban Dictionary application. 

**Security**

We take precautions to ensure the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that hackers or unauthorized personnel may gain access to your personal information despite our efforts. You should note that in using the Urban Dictionary service, your information will travel through third party infrastructures which are not under our control. 

We cannot protect, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to, any information that you transmit to other users. You should never transmit personal or identifying information to other users. 

**Children**

The Urban Dictionary service is not intended for children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. 

Children aged 13 or older should not submit any personal information without the permission of their parents or guardians. By using the Urban Dictionary service, you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents' or guardians' permission to use the service. 

**Changes**

Urban Dictionary may periodically update this policy. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions**

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to this address: [legal@urbandictionary.com](mailto:legal@urbandictionary.com)   
Or by mail at: Urban Dictionary LLC, Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiries, PO Box 7775, ECM #82617, San Francisco, CA 94120 

Updated: November 2008 

Copyright © 2008 Urban Dictionary, LLC
